One more lesson to share. The price of honor. The power of friendship.
And the way you must fight when only the winner survives.
The Karate Kid Part II is a adventure, drama, action
film directed by John G. Avildsen.
Summoned by his dying father, Miyagi returns to his homeland of
Okinawa, with Daniel, after a 40-year exile.
There he must confront Yukie, the love of his youth, and Sato,
his former best friend turned vengeful rival.
Sato is bent on a fight to the death, even if it
means the destruction of their village.
Daniel finds his own love in Yukia's niece, Kumiko, and his
own enemy in Sato's nephew, the vicious Chozen.
Now, far away from the tournaments, cheering crowds and safety of home, Daniel will
face his greatest challenge ever when the cost of honor is life itself.
Daniel LaRusso, played by Ralph Macchio.
Mr. Miyagi, played by Pat Morita.
Sato Toguchi, played by Danny Kamekona.
Yukie, played by Nobu McCarthy.
Chozen Toguchi, played by Yuji Okumoto.
Kumiko, played by Tamlyn Tomita.
The Karate Kid Part II is a 1986 American martial arts drama film
written by Robert Mark Kamen and directed by John G.
It is the second installment in The Karate Kid franchise and the sequel to the
1984 film The Karate Kid, starring Ralph Macchio and Pat Morita.
The Karate Kid Part II follows Daniel LaRusso (Macchio),
who accompanies his karate teacher Mr.
Miyagi (Morita) to see his dying father in Okinawa, only to encounter an old
friend-turned-rival with a long-harbored grudge against Miyagi.
Following the success of the first installment,
preparation for a sequel began immediately.
Upon completion of the final script, Macchio and Morita were re-signed and
additional casting took place between May and July 1985.
Principal photography began in September in Los
Angeles, and filming completed in December.
Locations included Oahu, which was used to represent Okinawa in the film.
The Karate Kid Part II was theatrically released in
the United States on June 20, 1986.
The film received mixed reviews, with critics praising Morita's performance as well as the new location and
characters, while others criticized elements of the storyline, the antagonists, and some of the action scenes.
The film was a commercial success, grossing $130 million worldwide (the same amount as
the first film), making it one of the highest-grossing films of 1986.
A sequel titled The Karate Kid Part III was released in 1989.
The film explores themes of underdog, martial
arts, japan, sports, death of father.
The tone is emotional.